<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">

<channel>
<title>&amp;#26085;&amp;#12293;&amp;#12398;&amp;#26412;</title>
<link>http://journal/</link>
<description></description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:creator>nemesisv@io.com</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2003-07-28T23:32:52-06:00</dc:date>
<admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.movabletype.org/?v=2.64" />
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updateBase>2000-01-01T12:00+00:00</sy:updateBase>

<item>
<title>Monday.2003.07.28.23:32:52</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Maybe that&apos;s why the alleged cruising incident happened -- I looked so hot, even a straight guy wanted to sleep with me. Ha!</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">893@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-28T23:32:52-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Saturday.2003.07.26.22:09</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Interesting. Here I&apos;ve been thinking about taking up guitar lessons again, and what should happen today at the store? My guitar teacher is in line and spots me behind the register. I&apos;m amazed after two years he still remembered my name. (I guess I was an all right student.) I...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">892@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-26T22:09:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Friday.2003.07.25.23:39</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>I&apos;m having fun with writing testimonials on Friendster. Most of them consist of inside jokes, but that doesn&apos;t stop me from sharing them here. It&apos;s a challenge trying to write something that could be construed as flattery without having to sacrifice wit. She&apos;s tangy -- not bitter. Omar is not...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">891@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-25T23:39:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Thursday.2003.07.24.23:52</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Um. I got an entry, but it&apos;s still in the works. It&apos;s pretty incoherent, and it may end up being a secret entry. (Haven&apos;t seen those in a long time, have you?) I suggest you read the latest Agonippe update instead. Update: Saturday.2003.07.26.23:02 Yup. It is indeed a secret entry....</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">890@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-24T23:52:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wednesday.2003.07.23.22:32</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>A sequel to &quot;19 Short Paragraphs in a Single Journal Entry&quot; ... it&apos;s called &quot;8 Ruled Lines&quot; ... I really have to remember to make Mozilla Firebird my default browser. The only thing I hate is now I have to use styles to control ruled lines. Forget about that whole...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">889@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-23T22:32:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tuesday.2003.07.22.22:35</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>I was going to make a list of things I&apos;d do if/when this new job turns permanent. But really, there&apos;s only one item on that list: take guitar lessons again. Over the weekend, my music books from Amazon Japan arrived -- faster than I expected! -- and some of the...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">888@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-22T22:35:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Monday.2003.07.21.22:29</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Little by little, they straggle in. The blues musicians on a Sunday evening. The restaurant is nearly deserted, the dinner rush nowhere near starting. She and I were probably the only lay people in the audience -- everyone else was carrying instruments. Guitar cases. Drumsticks. Harmonicas. Slowly but surely, the...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">887@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-21T22:29:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sunday.2003.07.20.23:55</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>I met with Gay Friend-Drinking Buddy this past Saturday. Yeah. I can scarcely believe I&apos;m typing that sentence myself. It&apos;s been four years since we&apos;ve actually talked face-to-face. He&apos;s e-mailed me about once-a-year, and we&apos;ll have a brief exchange. But that&apos;s pretty much it. Last week, he sent a message...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">886@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-20T23:55:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Thursday.2003.07.17.23:35</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>I have a new toy. It&apos;s not an electronic gadget like a handheld device. Nor is it a new fangled piece of web development software. No. My new toy is a dictionary. Not just any dictionary, mind you -- it&apos;s The Kodansha Kanji Learner&apos;s Dictionary. From the text: &quot;It contains...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">885@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-17T23:35:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tuesday.2003.07.15.23:16</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>All right. Here&apos;s that entry about funny record store signs. Problem is, I&apos;m not remembering even a fraction of the funnier stuff I&apos;ve seen tacked on the walls of the store in the last few months. That&apos;s what I get for dragging my sorry ass. So it&apos;s not much of...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">884@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-15T23:16:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Monday.2003.07.14.00:52</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Where does a person in Austin go at 11 p.m. when he&apos;s struck with an urge to get one of those chocolate-chip cookies sold at the mall? I like routines. There&apos;s a fine line between ruts and routines, and I probably wallow in ruts and convince myself they&apos;re routines. But...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">883@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-14T00:52:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sunday.2003.07.06.00:28</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>If this journal entry were a film, it would be called &quot;19 Short Paragraphs In a Single Journal Entry&quot;. Must. Resist. Temptation. To geek. Amazon is currently beta testing its web services for Japan, and as a result, I stumbled on a way to use XML to deliver lyrics in...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">882@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-06T00:28:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tuesday.2003.07.01.21:07</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>Dear GREGORY BUENO, (Hey, sucker,) We are pleased to inform you that we have raised the credit line of your Citi Platinum Select account to $_,___. (How ya like to use another G of our fake money?) This increase is a result of our ongoing credit review program. (We know...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">881@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-07-01T21:07:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sunday.2003.06.29.22:42</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>I think the last time I ever stepped foot into Oilcan Harry&apos;s was on my birthday in April 2000. I&apos;m lousy with math, so all the while I&apos;ve been saying it&apos;s been four years since I&apos;ve been there, it&apos;s really been three. (It&apos;s been four years since I stopped dating,...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">880@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-06-29T22:42:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>
<item>
<title>Friday.2003.06.27.22:45</title>
<link>http://journal/entry.php?entry=/</link>
<description>So. The Supreme Court has ruled Texas sodomy laws as unconstitutional. This is a galvanizing victory for conservative ideology nationwide. Now that states can&apos;t criminalize private sexual behavior between consenting adults, legislators throughout the country must now push through constitutional amendments limiting the definition of sex to a man and...</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">879@http://journal/</guid>
<dc:subject></dc:subject>
<dc:date>2003-06-27T22:45:00-06:00</dc:date>
</item>


</channel>
</rss>